South Africa

□ (+27) 67-076-0373 | Thandohimself@gmail.com | Athandohimself.github.io/ | □ Thandohimself

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary

Software engineer with experience in multiple settings can design and develop programs using the latest and most appropriate technology. Coder who loves version control, OS X and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Work Experience _____

immedia Umhlanga, KwaZulu-Natal

INTERN (HEAD START) May. 2019 - Present

- Migrated Java Features into Kotlin
- Implemented Fabrik POC'S
- Creation of Fabrik Tenants, e.g., Durban Girls' College, ASAIPA...to name a few
- Implemented UI & UX improvements across Codebase

immedia Umhlanga, KwaZulu-Natal

INTERN (HEAD START) MULTICHOICE (CAMPUS LIFE MOBILE APPLICATION)

- · Worked Closely with CMS team ensuring mobile application content was well aligned with Campus Life CMS
- Implemented UI improvements across mobile application

immedia Umhlanga, KwaZulu-Natal

INTERN (HEAD START) MULTICHOICE(SUPERSPORT MOBILE APPLICATION)

- Migrated & Developed SuperSport mobile application into Xamarin • Consumed SuperSport Rest API and implemented Sign-in Feature
- Bug-fixes & Weekly Team Testing the SuperSport mobile application

Umhlanga, KwaZulu-Natal immedia

INTERN (WORK INTEGRATED LEARNING (WIL))

- MVVM design pattern
- · Consuming Rest APIs
- · C# language
- · Visual Studio IDE
- GIT flow
- Xamarin
- · Scrum and Agile methodology

511 Griffiths Mxenge Hwy, Umlazi, Durban, 4031

FINAL YEAR PROJECT (QVAYAAPP)

- Jan. 2018 June. 2018 • Developed a Student Bus notification smartphone application which connects bus drivers and students.
- Implemented overall Android application logic and wrote PHP Scripts for community service, along with team engineers.
- Designed and implemented QvayaApp UI & UX.

Mangosuthu University of Technology

HyperionDev Remote

STUDENT ONLINE BOOT CAMP PROGRAM

Dec. 2015 - Feb. 2016

Jan. 2019 - May. 2019

Jan. 2019 - May. 2019

Jun. 2018 - Dec. 2018

· Completed Java course

Honors & Awards

BRETTONWOOD HIGH SCHOOL

Head Boys Award, Prefect Award Ceremony

Durban, KwaZulu-Natal

Presentation

THANDO LANGA · RÉSUMÉ 2019

Final Year Project Presentation

QVAYA APP FILM DIRECTOR AND EDITOR

- Directed and collaborated with team members in preparations for Qvaya App Film
- Edited and released Film
- Short Film link available upon request

Education

Mangosuthu University of Technology

DIPLOMA IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

• Software Development Stream.

511 Griffiths Mxenge Hwy, Umlazi,Durban, 4031

Jun. 2018

511 Griffiths Mxenge Hwy, Umlazi,Durban, 4031

Jan. 2016 - Aug. 2018